

1800 102 2558 | +91 9818882211







Head -Digital Process Automation seeking roles in Project Management, Program Management, Digital Transformation, Hybrid Integration, Robotic Process Automation, Practice Management, Pega RPA, UIPath, Automation Anywhere, BluePrism, Oracle, PEGA, TIBCO, Mulesoft



Total Experience: 24 Year(s) 0 Month(s)

Highest Degree: MCA[Computers]

Current Location: Bengaluru / Bangalore

Pref. Location: Bengaluru / Bangalore, Pune, Hyderabad

Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: Head/VP/GM-Technology(IT)/CTO Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Married

Key Skills: Head -Digital Process Automation, VP/GM-Technology(IT)/CTO, Project Management, Program Management, Digital Transformation, Robotic Process Automation, Practice Management, Pega RPA, UIPath, Automation

Anywhere, BluePrism, Oracle, PEGA, TIBCO, Mules oft

Verified: Phone Number | Email - id

Last Active: 19-Jan-21 Last Modified: 19-Jan-21

Jump to Section

Work Experience | Education | IT Skills |

Summary

Experienced IT professional having 24 years of multifaceted expertise in lifecycle facilitation to actualize large-scale engineering and delivery management of mission critical projects in Enterprise Digital Transformation and Automation, Hybrid Integration, BPM, Cloud Native App development and legacy modernization.

My last role was Global Head of Digital Process Automation for HappiestMinds Technologies Limited focusing on Pega and Appian based digital process automation implementations, Cognitive Automation using Al/ML technologies and Robotic process Automation using leading tools sets of Pega RPA, UIPath, Automation Anywhere and BluePrism.

Work Experience

Happiest Minds Technologies LTD as Head -Digital Process Automation Jan 2020 to Aug 2020

HappiestMnds Technologies is a USD 100 M+ leading Digital Transformation services provider with branding of "Born Digital ,Born Agile", focusing on cutting edge Digital technologies including intelligent BPMs /DPA tools viz Pega and Appian, Digital Integration using API /micro services and iPaaS platforms of Mulesoft, Tibco etc.

I have joined in Jan 2020 as part of their core leadership team, to focus on establishing a world class Digital process automation CoE with core focus on hyper automation services using RPA platforms like Ulpath ,Automation Anywhere and Blueprism, digital process automation platforms like Appian and Pega along with cognitive Process automation using AI/ML and DL technologies as well. Built a team of 100 + RPA people in Uipath and other RPA areas; achieved a run rate of 10MUSD for the RPA practice for FY 20.

Some of the highlights during my tenure as the Practices Head, are as below

- * Built a team of 100 + RPA people in Uipath and other RPA areas; achieved a run rate of 10MUSD for the RPA practice for FY20
- * Created solid pipeline of around 15 Mfor Intelligent automation using Appian, Pega and Mulesoft
- * Partnerships with a series of automation vendors in Al based Automation space to strengthen overall Automation offerings Viz, Softomotive (RPA vendor acquired by Mcrosoft), Baystree, Autonomiq, Enate etc
- * Though leadership articles and presentations in global forums on digital automation offerings so as to create brand awareness for HMs DPA offerings
- * Many of the marque customer acquisitions in DPA and Automation space

NIIT Incessant Pvt LTD as Head -Digital Process Automation Feb 2018 to Sep 2019

NIIT Incessant Private Limited, a subsidiary of Coforge Limited (formerly NIIT technologies) was USD 105 Million Digital process Automation company with core focus on BPM tools from Pega ,Appian etc and Digital integration tools of IBM.Mules oft . Tibco etc

I was handling the Digital Automation BU with P&L ownership of \$ 105 M for the organization which includes the comprehensive ownership of Delivery, Practices (DPA, Al, Integration and BPM), Innovations and Solutions and Global operations. Digital Process Automation Practices includes Cognitive Computing Practices (Al, ML, NLP, IoT/ M2M, RPA & Block Chain), Customer Experience Practices (User Experience (UET), Mobile, Analytics, Big data , ECM), Customer Engagement Practices (EAI, BPM, CRM, Agile /DevOps).

Important

· Using Free CV Search you have access to featured candidate profiles of Naukri. You can browse through the profiles and email the candidates of your choice directly using the email option provided. To prevent misuse of candidate information, contact details and attached resume of the candidates have been withheld

With team size of 1600 + people, our Focus verticals are BFSI, Manufacturing, CPG, Retail, Utilities, Telecom and travel /transportation and Government Some of the highlights during my tenure as the Practices Head, are as below

Positioned NIIT Incessant technologies as a Strong Performer by Forrester in Forrester Wave™: Digital Process Automation Service Providers, Q3 2018

Received Best Partner -Customer success Award from PegaSystems in Pegaworld 2018 &2019
Best IT Partner for APAC region award received from Appian corporation during Appian world 2018 in May 2018.
Our core thrust on Cloud +Cognitive Digital process automation area resulted in an order book of around \$ 145 Mfor the next 6 quarters.

Mphasis Ltd as Vice President & Practice Head -Digital Dec 2015 to Jan 2018

Mphasis Limited is USD 1Billion plus Enterprise IT services provider. Digital practices of Mphasis includes Cognitive Computing Practices (A,M_,NLP, loT/ M2M, RPA & Blockchain), Customer Experience Practices (User Experience (UET), Mobile, Analytics, Big data, ECM), Customer Engagement Practices (EAI,BPM,CRM, Agile (DevCos).

I owned the P&L, Strategy, Thought Leadership and Delivery for these practices with team size of 1400 + people with Annual target for FY 17-18 is USD 65 M Our Focus verticals are BFSI, Manufacturing, CPG, Retail, Utilities, Telecom and travel /transportation.

Also I was a key member of Digital Strategy and Innovation council for Mphasis Limited reporting to CEO, Responsibilities of this team include evangelizing and finalizing Mphasis digital offerings to customers and Identify validate and approve cross practices digital solutions in collaboration with partners and pilot customers. The core focus service areas are

Enterprise Digital Transformation Services using Cognitive platforms implementations using NLP, RPA, Machine Learning and Al), Digital Transformation through intelligent BPMs, SMACT enablement for dynamic enterprises, Cloud and API integration, Integration platforms as Services(IPaaS), BPaaS and IoT/M2Mfor business process optimization Integration Platform as Services(iPaaS), Cloud integration, API Economy/ Integration services, IoT integration, Cloud app development /Refactoring

^ Back to Top

Education

UG: BCA (Computers) from Dr Babasaheb Ambedkar Marathwada University, Aurangabad in 1993 PG: MCA (Computers) from Dr Babasaheb Ambedkar Marathwada University, Aurangabad in 1996

^ Back to Top

IT Skills

Skill Name	Version Last Used	Experience
Pega RPA		
Uipath		
Automation Anywhere		
BluePrism		
J2EE		
Oracle		
Tibco		
MICROSOFT		

^ Back to Top

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English				
Hindi				
Tamil				
Kannada				
Malayalam				

^ Back to Top

Affirmative Action

Work Authorization

Physically Challenged: No

Job Type: Permanent Employment Status: Full time

^ Back to Top

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQ's - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICIClcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.